bop.fm 2015-03-19

# bop.fm

## Privacy Policy

Bop FM, Inc ("bop.fm") respects your privacy and recognizes the need for appropriate protection and management of your personal information, such as your name, email address and any other personally identifiable information you may provide to us. None of this information is currently required to utilize our service, though certain components of our service may require registration.

bop.fm does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to marketers. We may use your personal information to contact you from time to time regarding updates to our policies, upgrades to our software, or other information that we feel may be of interest to you.

bop.fm has publicly available profiles where you may share music you love using various social media and other channels. This publicly available profile requires a valid email address and/or social media account access authorizations.

Although we do not sell, trade or rent your information, we may release personal and/or non-personal information about you when you request us to do so. In addition, your information may also be accessed by bop.fm employees as necessary to provide customer support and troubleshoot problems.

We may also release personal and non-personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements, or to protect the rights of bop.fm or others. Information collected about you is protected in several ways. Access by you to your personal information if you sign up for an account is available through a password and unique user ID. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone and change it often.

Your personal information resides on proprietary and secure servers on Amazon Web Services. Only selected bop.fm personnel and contracts have access to it via password. The Amazon Web Services facilities are subject to the terms and conditions of Amazon's Web Services Licensing Agreement.

At any time, you may request to view or update the personal information that is associated with your account and stored by bop.fm. You may also request that we delete all personal and/or non-personal information that we have collected about you. We will promptly fulfill your request and provide you confirmation when the information has been deleted.

Because the Internet is constantly evolving, so are our policies. By agreeing to our terms of service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as it may be amended from time to time. While we may send you a copy of any updates, we recommend that you check back to view the policy at this site from time to time.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact bop.fm at [info@bop.fm](mailto:info@bop.fm).
